alifeinbalance.net 2014-06-18

# privacy policy | A Life in Balance

_Disclosure: If you make a purchase using a link on this page, I may earn a commission and I am very grateful for your support of this site. Thank you. ([Read all the fine print here](http://alifeinbalance.net/about/disclosure/).)_  

_Effective Date: April 13, 2013_

A Life in Balance and Frugal Local Kitchen respect and value your privacy.

This Privacy Policy details how A Life in Balance and Frugal Local Kitchen (hereinafter referred to as “ALB/FLK, “us” or “we”) treats the information that is gathered about you when you use the A Life in Balance and Frugal Local Kitchen websites, [alifeinbalance.net](http://alifeinbalance.net/) and frugallocalkitchen.com (hereinafter referred to as the “Sites”). By using and commenting on ALB and FLK, you expressly consent to the collection, use, disclosure and storage of such information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### Collection of Information:

#### Non Personally Identifiable Information (Cookies):

ALB and FLK use cookies solely for internal recordkeeping, external statistics about our users as a whole and aggregating data about the traffic on these Sites. If you would prefer not to have cookies on your computer, you can block by selecting that option on your computer and/or internet browser. These Sites gathers IP addresses from all visitors to the Site and may use this information in a variety of ways including, but not limited to, research purposes.

#### Personally Identifiable Information:

When you sign up on the Sites to receive email announcements, send an email to ALF/FLK and/or comment on a post, ALB or FLK may require that you provide certain personally identifiable information which may include, but is not necessarily limited to:

* first and last name,  
* email address; and  
* blog URL

ALB or FLK may also request other personally identifiable information, which you may choose whether or not to provide which is treated in the same manner as all other personally identifiable information under this privacy policy.

### Use of Personally Identifiable Information:

ALB/FLK will use the personally identifiable information that we collect about you to contact you in response to consumer-initiated inquiries, to provide the services to you that you request, to alert you to changes in services or features, to provide newsletters and/or announcements and to provide you with requested information regarding ALB/FLK.

ALB/FLK reserve the right to release current or past user information:  
(a) In the event that we believe that the Site is being or has been used to commit unlawful acts;  
(b) Upon receipt of a properly authorized and authenticated governmental request for information;  
(c) In response to a subpoena or a court order,  
(d) To comply with relevant laws;  
(e) In response to an investigation of fraud or other wrongdoing regarding a specific consumer; or  
(f) In an effort to safeguard the person or property of a ALB/FLK employee or a third party.

Moreover, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when ALB/FLK, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time.

If you no longer wish to receive emails from us which you have not specifically initiated, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable e-mail. ALB/FLK processes all unsubscribe requests in a prompt fashion.

#### International Users:

By using the Site and providing ALB/FLK with data, you understand and agree that due to the international dimension of the Internet, ALB/FLK may use the data collected in the course of our relationship as set forth in this Privacy Policy or in other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, you acknowledge that your personally identifiable information and other data may be stored on servers located in the United States or in other international locations. By providing us with your information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information.

#### Third Party Sites:

ALB/FLK may direct you to third party websites. Those websites are not affiliated with ALB/FLK and their privacy policies may differ from ALB/FLK’s privacy policy. ALB/FLK is in no way responsible for the privacy policies or treatment of information from third party websites and strongly encourages you to review the privacy policies of every website you visit to determine what information they collect and how such information is handled by that website.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.lijit.com/company/privacy-policy> and <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>.

### Storage of Information:

We are serious about the security of your personal information. We limit access to your personally identifiable information to those individuals (i.e., our employees and agents) who we reasonably believe need to have access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

Your personally identifiable information is stored on our servers located in the United States. ALB/FLK treats your data as an asset that must be protected and use many tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. Although ALB/FLK does not release your personally identifiable information to the public and ALB/FLK makes a reasonable good faith effort to store your personally identifiable information in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee 100% security of such information due to factors beyond our control.

### Access or Questions:

If you have any questions about our privacy policy or wish to review, or revise the personally identifiable information that ALB/FLK has collected about you, you may send a written request to:

A Life in Balance  
1141 Villanova Avenue  
Swarthmore, PA 19081

ALB/FLK may take reasonable steps to confirm your identity prior to supplying any personally identifiable information to you in order to prevent identity theft.

### Acceptance of and Changes to this Privacy Policy:

By using ALB/FLK, you hereby agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety. ALB/FLK reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time.

All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or failure to opt-out of emails sent to you following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of any and all changes.

_A Life in Balance is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. See more at:<http://marketingwithsara.com/amazon/warning-to-all-affiliate-marketers#sthash.7pLtrFUN.dpuf>_

_I share because I care, so feel free to use any of my images as long as they are credited and accompanied by a link back to[A Life in Balance](http://www.alifeinbalance.net/). Failure to link back and credit my site as a source constitutes a copyright violation. Thanks!_
